Phone: 512-800-5860 http://stuart.weenig.com

HIGHLIGHTS OF QUALIFICATIONS

- Agile Scrum Project Management
- Ansible Network Automation
- Customer Centric Solution Selling
- SharePoint
- Windows 10

- MS Office 365
- Process Analysis
- NetQoS Suite
- Dynamic Problem-Solver
- ITIL Framework
- Data Center Infrastructure

- Process Improvement
- VMWare
- Fortune 100 Experience
- Remedy Enterprise Incident Management
- Technology/Multimedia Production

LANGUAGE/PROTOCOL/TECHNOLOGY FLUENCY

- Python
- YAML
- Ansible
- HTML5/CSS 3/JavaScript

- Perl
- NetFlow/IPFIX
- TCP/IP
- Class Based QoS
- SNMP

- PHP
- SQL
 - Spanish

(Read/Write/Speak)

SIGNIFICANT PROFESSIONAL SUCCESSES

DEVELOPED Ansible playbook for upgrading Cisco IOS devices en masse, certified to work against 10 common Cisco models using open source software development methodologies and Git.

DESIGNED an enterprise Level 1 Network Operations Center (NOC) including supporting applications, databases, workflows, and processes to ensure seamless transition from outsourced NOC to in-sourced NOC. Resulting in \$10M/year decrease in operational expenses for Network Operations.

ENGINEERED and **DEPLOYED** an alarm aggregation and event management system using southbound integrations to the enterprise ticketing system resulting in faster ticket generation time with higher quality embedded data.

RETAINED more than 50 Fortune 100 companies in through monitoring of networks for availability, performance, and configuration.

PROVIDED continuous research, assessment, recommendations, and implementation of new technologies to customers.

PRODUCED training curriculum, videos, and other multi-media to lead, mentor and coach peers on operations processes and technology.

ADOPTED design, implementation, maintenance, and support recommendations to customers needs.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science; Electrical Engineering - Louisiana Tech University, Ruston, LA

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

National Oilwel Varco, Houston, TX - Software Developer

2014 - 2018

- Assist with automation initiatives to decrease deployment time of oil well services applications.
- Guide the deployment team in the use of Agile Scrum.
- Coordinate efforts to Dockerize applications for ease of deployment.
- Engineer optimized networking solutions for on-rig equipment as well as lab environments.
- > Automate network engineering tasks using Ansible.

Chevron, Houston, TX - Senior NMS Analyst

2014 - 2018

> Chief Architect for network automation including development, testing, and mass deployment of production OS upgrades, Security Controls Compliance, and best practices configuration.

E-mail: stuart@weenig.com Phone: 512-800-5860 http://stuart.weenig.com

- > Designed business decision data repository using software development lifecycle methodologies for automated/zero touch provisioning of production infrastructure through Ansible Tower.
- Principal developer for Ansible Playbook for upgrading Cisco IOS devices en masse, certified for use against the ten most common models of Cisco devices.
- Enterprise Tools Portfolio Management responsibilities including deduplication, renovation, modernization, and rationalization of tools currently in use globally.
- As SharePoint Team Site administrator, identified growth opportunities and filled gaps using out of the box technologies, maximizing utilization and convenience.
- ldentified and prepared for long term growth of network operations monitoring pipeline to include server, cloud, storage, database, and application monitoring.
- Proactively identify network infrastructure issues by providing regular, clear, reliable communication to stake holders about service impacting issues.
- Organized and carried out PiWars coding principles education initiative, utilizing low budget robotics and physical computing devices.

Aspire Technical Professionals – NetQoS Architect/Technical Project Architect 2012 – 2014

- > Project management of all direct to customer and third party customer technical consulting projects.
- > Conduct strategy identification with key customer stake holders to define statements of work and scopes.
- > Architect solutions based on needs extracted from customer conversations and requirement documentation.
- Provide in depth insight into pre-sales and post-sales strategies.
- > Consulted NetQoS customers on the installation, configuration, and optimization of network monitoring tools, including CA NetQoS Unified Communications Monitoring.
- > Inform customers of strategic direction and needed emphasis with regard to network, server, and application infrastructure to increase performance and reliability.

Research In Motion - System Engineering Specialist

2010 - 2011

- Implement, configure, troubleshoot, and interpret I.T. resource performance as dictated by enterprise I.T. as well as BlackBerry® I.T.
- Evaluate and document product functionality of Service Assurance tools according to customer business needs.
- Upgrade and maintain staging and production IT monitoring tools in accordance with enterprise change management requirements.
- Create custom data collection, reports, and notifications for 3rd party hardware and software.

Republic National Distributing Company – Windows/Network Engineer

2009 - 2010

- > Design, implement, monitor, and troubleshoot the enterprise network for performance optimization and service availability; align I.T. resources to business needs.
- Monitor enterprise I.T. resources for performance degradation. Recommend and manage changes to improve service availability and performance.
- Maintain monitoring software for automatic alarming. Research and drive projects and changes to shift I.T. systems to support business needs.

NetQoS, Inc.

2006 - 2009

Technical Consultant, 2008 - 2009

- > Charged with implementing technology to decrease the on-boarding time of new employees.
- > Designed and built the next generation training lab in accordance with training department needs.
- Expanded customer potential by authoring best practices and training material. Creation of collegiate-level papers detailing expertise in network performance monitoring. Developed best practices documentation on a regular schedule.
- Created fully automated training lab reset procedures and managed the lab resets.

Networking Consultant, 2006 - 2008

- In charge of increasing customer capabilities to ensure maintenance renewals and future purchases.
- Conducted week-long training sessions with customers. Engaged to highly customize training based on customer environments and business needs.
- > Analyzed customer environments and drew business needs from stakeholders in order to modify and conduct on premise training.

www.linkedin.com/in/sweenig Page 3 of 3 E-mail: stuart@weenig.com Phone: 512-800-5860 http://stuart.weenig.com

Product Support Specialist, 2006

- > In charge of resolving customer issues to ensure maintenance renewal and future purchases.
- > Solved problems with NetQoS products in less than 2 hours. Charged with becoming the subject matter expert for and disseminating troubleshooting methods for newly acquired products.
- Fielded incoming customer requests. Provided customer service for upgrades, installations, and customizations.

CA|NetQoS Global User Community - NetQoS Global Community Officer

2010 - 2015

- > Served as acting president forming the NetQoS Global User Community group consisting of 300 customers across the globe.
- Served as Communications Officer moderating the public message boards and implementing social media integration and syndication to Twitter, Facebook, and LinkedIn.
- Grew membership to almost 600 members in 18 months.
- Coordinated the merger of the NetQoS community with the Spectrum/eHealth community.
- > Presided at the global user meetings held at CA World in Las Vegas.